{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "x", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 6, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 6, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^6√x^6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(5/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 5, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(5/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(5/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 10, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(5/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(9/4)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 9, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(9/4).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^3", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 9, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^3.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(3/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 6, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(3/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 10, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^2.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(2/5)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 2, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(2/5).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(9/4)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 9, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(9/4).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(9/4)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 9, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(9/4).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(5/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 5, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(5/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(1/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 2, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(1/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(6/5)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 6, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(6/5).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(3/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 9, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 6, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(3/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^6√x^9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 8, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^2.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(7/4)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 7, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(7/4).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(5/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 10, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 6, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(5/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^6√x^10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(3/4)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 3, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(3/4).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(3/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 6, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(3/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(3/5)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 3, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(3/5).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(7/6)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 7, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 6, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(7/6).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^6√x^7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(8/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 8, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(8/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(9/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 9, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 2, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(9/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n√x^9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(9/4)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 9, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(9/4).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(3/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 6, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(3/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(9/4)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 9, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(9/4).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(5/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 5, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(5/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(8/5)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 8, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(8/5).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^4", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 8, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 2, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^4.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n√x^8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(3/4)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 3, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(3/4).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(9/5)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 9, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(9/5).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(7/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 7, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 2, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(7/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n√x^7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(5/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 10, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(5/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^3", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 9, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^3.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(5/4)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 5, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(5/4).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(4/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 4, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(4/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(3/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 9, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 6, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(3/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^6√x^9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(2/5)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 2, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(2/5).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(4/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 4, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(4/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(2/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 2, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(2/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(5/6)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 5, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 6, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(5/6).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^6√x^5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(9/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 9, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 2, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(9/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n√x^9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(1/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 3, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 6, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(1/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^6√x^3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(4/5)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 4, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(4/5).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 3, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 6, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^2.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(3/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 3, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 2, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(3/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n√x^3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(2/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 2, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(2/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(7/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 7, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 2, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(7/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n√x^7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(8/5)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 8, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(8/5).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(1/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 3, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 6, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(1/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^6√x^3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(4/5)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 4, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(4/5).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 4, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 2, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^2.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n√x^4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 5, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(2/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 2, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(2/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 8, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^2.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(9/4)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 9, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(9/4).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(3/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 6, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(3/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 5, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(5/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 5, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(5/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 5, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^5", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 10, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 2, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^5.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n√x^10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(8/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 8, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(8/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(7/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 7, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 2, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(7/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n√x^7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(5/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 5, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 2, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(5/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n√x^5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 2, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 2, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n√x^2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(5/4)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 5, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(5/4).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(2/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 2, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(2/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(6/5)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 6, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(6/5).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(7/5)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 7, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(7/5).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(2/5)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 2, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(2/5).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(5/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 10, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(5/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(4/5)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 4, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(4/5).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(4/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 8, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 6, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(4/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^6√x^8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(5/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 5, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 2, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(5/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n√x^5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(2/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 2, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(2/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^3", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 9, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^3.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 8, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^2.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(5/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 10, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(5/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(5/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 10, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(5/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(1/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 2, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 6, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(1/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^6√x^2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(7/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 7, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(7/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(7/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 7, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(7/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^3", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 9, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^3.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(5/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 5, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(5/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(8/5)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 8, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(8/5).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 6, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^2.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 3, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 3, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^3√x^3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(2/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 4, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 6, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(2/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^6√x^4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(1/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 3, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 6, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(1/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^6√x^3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(9/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 9, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 2, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(9/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n√x^9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 10, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^2.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(4/5)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 4, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(4/5).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(5/6)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 5, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 6, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(5/6).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^6√x^5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(7/5)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 7, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(7/5).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(7/6)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 7, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 6, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(7/6).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^6√x^7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(3/2)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 6, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 4, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(3/2).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^4√x^6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(2/5)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 2, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 5, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(2/5).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^5√x^2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^(4/3)", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 8, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 6, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x^(4/3).", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^6√x^8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x", "explanation": "Create a fraction where 6, the exponent of the variable, is the numerator and 6, the degree of the root, is the denominator.\n\nMake this fraction the exponent of the variable. The answer is x.", "question": "Express as an exponent:\n^6√x^6", "type": "text"}
]}